中学
恭喜你 Billy 你获得了最残障学生奖
Congratulations, Billy. You win most handicapped.
老子不服
This is bullshit.
接下来全校最潮最受欢迎学生奖将授予...
And now the award for coolest, most popular kid in school goes to...
Woody Johnson
Woody Johnson.
你是不是忘了啥 孩子?
Did you forget something, son?
你也就配得... 最诡异蛋蛋奖
The only award you'll win is weirdest looking balls.
卧槽
Damn!
他那两颗蛋好像在疯狂搅基
His balls look like they mad at each other.
这还没完呢 Johnson先生
More bad news, Mr. Johnson.
- 我还把你妈唤来了 - 不
- I called your mother. - No!
Woody 你可真是个淘气的孩子
Woody, you've been a bad boy.
- Woody - 不要啊 妈咪 不要伤害我
- Woody! - No, mommy! Don't hurt me!
- 又做噩梦了? - 是的 抱歉了 小伙计
- Another nightmare? - Yeah. Sorry, little buddy.
真够关心我
Oh, that's nice.
一句"对不起"肯定能治好我的肿头
No, I'm sure "sorry" stops brain swelling.
还好我没打坏奖状
Well, at least I didn't break my award.
最诡异蛋蛋奖
漫迪字幕组倾情奉献
脆莓公园
♢ 症 ♢ 偏执绝非过错
♢ 井脑湿 ♢ 旗木 联合译制
早上好 林警们 我有好消息
Good morning, rangers. I got great news.
天啊 Woody 你看起来状态真差
Jeez, Woody, you look terrible.
- 昨晚没睡好么? - 我睡得和往常一样香
- Did you sleep last night? - I slept perfectly normal.
没错 熟睡20分钟 其余7小时都在发疯般地尖叫
Yep, 20 minutes of sleep, 7 hours of intense screaming.
跟Ethel把振动棒插进自己时一样
Sounds like Ethel breaking in her vibrator.
慢着 我就是Ethel 也是醉了
Wait, I'm Ethel. Sorry, I'm drunk.
不要再调侃我的夜惊了
Oh, enough about my night terrors.
所以这就是你经常暴躁的原因了
So, that's why you're always so irritable.
- 我才不暴躁 - 敢跟你肠子这么说么?
- I am not irritable! - Tell that to your bowels.
懂了没?
You get it?
好好笑喔 现在克罗恩氏病也成梗儿了
Oh, ha ha. I guess crohn's disease is funny now.
炎性肠病
我勒个去 我拉裤子了
Oh, damn it, I just shit myself.
不管了 现在宣布好消息
Anyway, I got great news.
贝蒂·怀特: 90岁高龄美国演员
吞卡手电是一种男性自慰工具
- 你给咱买了贝蒂·怀特款吞卡手电? - 不是
- You bought us all Betty White fleshlights? - No.
你给我买了贝蒂·怀特款吞卡手电?
You bought me a Betty White fleshlight?
someone's coming也指某人要性高潮了
不是 要有人来了
No. Someone's coming.
给我个贝蒂·怀特款吞卡手电 我肯定能来
I will be, if I get my Betty White fleshlight.
闭嘴 是总统奥巴马要来脆莓公园了
Shut up! President Obama is coming to Brickleberry.
天啊 不 他发现了我
Oh, no. He found me.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
奥巴马对我很有性趣 那方面
Obama is really into me, sexually.
- 我能枪毙她么? - Connie 别发神经哟
- Can I shoot her? - Connie, stop being psycho.
就是 你想让我们相信黑人兄弟会对白人肥妞有性趣?
Yeah, you expect us to believe that a black guy could be into a fat, white woman?
能枪毙他么?
Can I shoot him?
- 求之不得 - 全都给我闭嘴
- Do us a favor. - Everyone, shut up.
总统此次到访是为了表彰我
The president is coming to honor me
作为林警三十年如一日地不间断出勤
for 30 years' perfect attendance as a park ranger.
慢着 我努力鸟你试试
Hold on, I'm trying to give a [Bleep].
算了 鸟你个肺
No, not happening.
必须确保在我的大日子里绝不能有屁事发生
We gotta make sure that nothing happens to ruin my big day.
Denzel 你负责安保工作和...
Denzel, you're in charge of security and...
等等 Woody 你又不待见奥巴马
Wait a minute, Woody, you don't even like Obama.
什么? 我爱死奥巴马了
What? I love Obama.
行了 你和Connie负责...
Now, you and Connie are in charge of
清理掉所有我用来反对奥巴马的东西
disposing of all my anti-Obama paraphernalia.
那我呢 Woody?
What's my assignment, Woody?
Steve 你的工作相比之下就是重中之重了
Steve, you have the most important job of all.
《冰与火之歌》中的城堡名
我需要你出差到君临城
I need you to travel to King's Landing
《冰与火之歌》中重要的POV角色之一
为我取回提利昂·兰尼斯特的人头
and bring me the head of Tyrion Lannister.
知名连锁西餐厅
君临城啊 是不是离乳酪蛋糕工厂不远?
King's landing... is that near the cheesecake factory?
对对对 随便哪里
Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever.
可我会错过你的盛典诶 Woody
But I'll miss your big ceremony, Woody.
没错 我就这意思 傻X
Yeah, that's the point, dumbass.
我是绝对不会让你有机会当着总统的面让我出糗的
There's no way I'm letting you embarrass me in front of the president.
我啥时候让你出过糗了?
When have I ever been an embarrassment?
弥撒: 天主教宗教仪式
你丫记不记得有次你在圣诞弥撒上喝醉了?
How about the time you got drunk at Christmas mass?
- 那你还是个处女喽? - 什么?
- So you're a virgin, huh? - What?!
我在和那头驴子说话呢
I was talking to the donkey.
真是不敢相信Woody竟然比其他人有资格和总统见面
I can't believe Woody, of all people, is getting to meet the president.
相信我吧 那没啥了不起的
Trust me, it's not that big of a deal.
Connie 你真指望我会相信你认识总统吗?
Connie, do you really expect me to believe that you know the president?
真的
I do.
我曾在他的竞选团队里担任过媒体顾问
I worked on his campaign as the media consultant.
他对我实在太饥渴 甚至一度要开除我
He wanted me so bad that he tried to fire me,
可惜他做不到 因为他对我的身体欲罢不能
but he couldn't because he was so hot for my body.
你先等等
Wait a minute.
你明明是在背《丑闻》里的台词
You're describing the TV show Scandal.
奥巴马的肯尼亚共和国出生证
我知道 那部剧就是根据我的生活改编的
I know. They based that show on my life.
Connie 你又和现实脱节了
Connie, you've lost touch with reality again.
还记得那次你说奥普拉要为了你和斯特德曼离婚么?
Remember that time you told everyone Oprah was gonna leave Stedman for you?
前者为脱口秀女主播 后者为纽约时报畅销书作家 二人系夫妻
是真的 她说想要把我的粉木耳玩成黑的
She was! She said she wanted to make my clitoris the color purple.
你觉得怎么样 Malloy?
What do you think, Malloy?
我整了这玩意加深总统对我的印象
I got these to impress the president.
有木有让哥变得更加智慧?
Do they make me look smarter?
比啥更智慧? 桌子嘛? 没有
Smarter than what? This table? No.
- Denzel 你特么地干啥呢? - 安全措施呀
- Denzel, what the hell are you doing? - Security measure.
我得把这电视抱回家仔细检查一下...
I've got to take this TV to my place to check it out for, uh...
是否藏有朝鲜脏弹
North Korean dirty bombs.
好吧 去我卧室看看有没更大的
Uh-oh, check the even bigger one in my bedroom.
红色警报 红色警报
Code red! Code red!
瑞士名表
- 一块真力时而已 - 去它丫的
- It's a Zenith. - Oh, [Bleep] that shit.
Woody 我搞到手了
Hey, Woody, I got it.
《冰与火之歌》中Tyrion Lannister扮演者
搞毛啊 Steve? 你把彼特·丁拉基的脑袋砍下来了?
What the [Bleep], Steve? You cut off Peter Dinklage's head?
没错 正如你所指示呀
Yeah, just like you asked.
他不停叫喊 "我只是个糟糕的演员
He kept screaming, "I'm just a bad actor!
他只是我所扮演的一个角色
"It's a role I play on a television show!
你为什么要对我下此毒手?
Ugh, why are you doing this to me?"
我只管专心锯他脖子
But I just kept sawing.
均为矮小症者
好吧 把他也挂上去吧
Oh, fine, mount it with the rest of them.
现在可以参加你表彰大典了吧?
So can I go to your ceremony now?
不行 我再给你安排份工作
No! I have another job for you.
我要你为总统挖一条逃生隧道
I need you to dig an escape tunnel for the president
用这个塑料小勺勺
with this plastic spoon.
- 挖到哪儿去? - 挖到肯尼亚他老窝儿去
- Where to? - Back to Kenya where he came from!
- 那个 我爱奥巴马 - 哇哦 帅气的眼镜
- I mean, I love Obama. - Hey, cool glasses.
嗨 我是Steve Williams教授
Hi, I'm Professor Steve Williams.
- 还给我 - 别
- Give me those. - Hey!
- 我的装逼眼镜啊 Steve - 我去挖隧道了
- My fake smart guy glasses! Steve! - Off to dig the tunnel.
我向天发誓
I swear to God,
再敢让我跟这逗逼过上一秒 我打爆丫的脑袋
if I have to spend another second with that dipshit, I'll shoot him.
所以你觉得我应该多花点时间陪陪Woody?
So you think I should spend more time with Woody?
一点不错
Absolutely.
一旦他对我了解更多 让我们成为刎颈之交
And once he gets to know me better and we become best friends,
他就会邀请我参加他的盛典?
he'll invite me to his big ceremony?
那必须的 别忘了在他耳边多来四五句说唱
Of course he will, and make sure to use lots of rap lingo.
- 他爱死说唱了 - 多谢了 Malloy
- Ah, he loves that. - Thanks, Malloy.
现在请让我安安心心挖完这段通往肯尼亚的隧道
Now, excuse me while I finish this tunnel to Kenya.
- 我马上就要... - 请问去奶酪蛋糕工厂怎么走?
- I'm al... - Can you tell us how to get to the cheesecake factory?
Bodean 俺不敢相信奥巴马要来了
Bodean, I can't believe Obama's coming here.
- 你和俺一样灰常不爽吗? - 不 我投了他的票
- Are you as pissed off as I am? - No, I voted for Obama.
- 你刚说啥来着? - 我说我投了...
- What did you say? - I said I voted for...
你丫被洗脑了
You been brainwashed!
你这些时都看的什么狗屎玩意?
What's that shit you been watching again?
- 唐顿庄园 - 又是洗脑玩意
- Downton Abbey. - Brainwashed!
Bodean 听俺说
Bodean, listen to me.
这些自由派的人要侵吞俺们的国家
These liberals are screwing up our country.
他们会禁烟 禁垃圾食品 拿走俺们的火器
They're gonna ban smoking and junk food, take our guns,
还很有可能让俺们结同性恋的婚呢
and probably make us gay marry each other.
- 俺蛮喜欢奥巴马医改 - 这是最恶心的事儿
- I kind of like Obamacare. - That's the worst part!
就算是俺都能想个比他更好的医改方案
Even I could come up with a better health care plan.
- 那为啥你不实施? - 或许有朝一日我会
- Why don't you do it then? - Maybe I will.
你又是哪根筋不对给奥巴马投票的?
Why the hell did you vote for Obama anyway?
因为收入不均是严重的社会问题
Because income inequality is a very significant social issue,
而右翼分子们推行的递减税政策又让其雪上加霜
and it's reinforced by a series of regressive tax reforms foisted upon us by right-wingers.
- 我醒着呢 Bodean - 我知道
- I'm awake, Bodean. - I know.
谢谢 总统先生
Thank you, Mr. president.
不对 谢谢您 总统先生
No. Thank you, Mr. president.
不对 谢谢您 总统阁下
No. Thank you, Mr. president!
不 你肯定会出糗的 Johnson
No, you're gonna screw it up, Johnson.
嘿 哥们
Hey, player,
小弟觉得咱们应该多花那么些个时间在一起聊聊
I thought wiggity-we should spend a little tiggity-time togevah.
只有大哥你和小弟Steve我
Just Big Dubs and Run-DM-Steve.
Steve 别怪我下毒手
Steve, I will murder you.
一起看《威利旺卡和那什么巧克力工厂》吗?
Wanna watch Willy wizzle and the chizzle fizzle?
- 我租了蓝光版本的哟 - 别怪我没警告你
- I rented it on blu-rizzle. - I'm warning you, Steve.
把派给他
Give him the pie.
噢 我给你做了个个个个个个个个个个...
Oh, I made you a p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-
个个个个个个个个个个个个个个个个个个个个个派
p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-pie!
真棒
Yes!
啊噢 我的那个个个个个派
Uh-oh, my p-cuh-p-cuh-p-cuh-pie.
不好 Malloy 快叫救护那啥车来
Oh, no. Malloy, call an ambu-lizzle!
Woody 我这里有好消息和坏消息 还有超级坏的消息
Woody, I have good news and bad news and super bad news.
超级坏的消息是什么?
What's the super bad news?
美国演员 导演
本·阿弗莱克会饰演新蝙蝠侠
Ben Affleck is the new Batman.
谁管这事啊?! 那我这儿呢?
Who gives a shit?! What about me?
Woody 你毁了你的肝脏
Woody, you destroyed your liver,
毁得彻彻底底傻X了
totally, well, [Bleep] It up.
好消息是 我这儿有现成的捐赠者肝脏
The good news is, I have a donor liver right here.
这可真是好消息
Oh, that's great, doc.
坏消息是 根据奥巴马健保手册第2242页的规定
The bad news is that according to page 2,242 of the Obamacare manual,
这份肝脏必须移植给一名非法移民的基佬
this liver must go to a gay, illegal immigrant.
我了个艹 福克斯新闻说得没错
Holy shit, Fox News was right.
Woody 我们找不到捐赠者 只有让你和人共享肝脏了
Woody, since we can't find you a liver, you'll be sharing one.
共享肝脏? 和谁?
Share a liver? With who?
- 好啊 肝友 - 什么?
- Hey, liver buddy! - What?
你怎能把我和这痴呆捆一起?
You attached me to this moron?
此处dialysis既指透析 也指人名
为什么不直接让我上透析?
Why didn't you just put me on dialysis?
相信我 Woody 我试过了 对吧 投茜?
Trust me, Woody, I tried. Isn't that right, Dialysis?
没人能上投茜 除非他和我结婚
Ain't nobody getting on dialysis unless they put a ring on it.
如果必须把我和别人缝起来
If you had to sew me to someone,
为什么得给我找这头蠢驴?
why did you have to pick captain dumbass?
诶呀 Woody 他是唯一自愿捐赠的人呀
Well, Woody, he was the only one who would volunteer.
这就是身为朋友的义务
'Cause that's what friends do.
如果你真想做我朋友
If you were a real friend,
就应该把肝脏整个给我然后去死
you would have just given me your liver and died!
这样更好 让我们有更多的机会了解彼此
This is even better. Now we can really get to know each other.
大夫 啥时能把这会说话的瘤子从我身上割掉?
Doc, when can you saw this talking tumor off of me?
我还要出席盛典呢
I got an event to go to.
我看看 这里说
Let's see. Actually, it says here that...
如果那个非法移民基佬48小时之内不需要肝脏捐赠的话
if a gay, illegal immigrant does not need the liver within 48 hours,
这肝脏就归你了
huh, it's all yours.
- 很好 刚好赶上我领奖前 - 说到拿奖
- Great, just in time to get my award. - Speaking of awards,
前奥运冠军 曾多次整容
你们有看过我的布鲁斯·詹那"医疗噩梦"奖杯吗?
have I shown you my Bruce Jenner "horrors of medicine" trophy?
Woody Johnson说 去屎吧 奥巴马
我们公园的头号景点这下算是玩完了
There goes our number one tourist attraction.
"让我享用享用你那肉颤颤的丰臀"
"Give me, give me some of that big, flappy ass."
- 谁发的这恶心玩意? - 呃 贝拉克
- Ew! Who is that from? - Ugh, Barack.
容我整理下思路
Let me get this straight.
美国总统刚给你发了条短信
The President of the United States of America just texted,
"让我享用享用你那肥美美的丰臀"
"give me, give me some of that big, floppy ass"?
- 不 他说的是"肉颤颤" - 让我看看
- No, he said, "flappy." - Let me see that.
能在用户指定时间内自动删除短信照片的App
- 我啥都没看到 - 我知道 他用的快照
- There's nothing there. - I know. He used a snapchat.
Connie 你最好在总统来之前停下这些胡思乱想
Connie, you better cut out this nonsense before the president gets here,
不然你就吃不了兜着走了
or you could get into some real trouble.
不是胡思乱想 Ethel 我发誓
It's not nonsense, Ethel, I swear.
"肉颤 肉颤 肉颤颤的丰臀 让你给我一发入魂"
"Flap, flap, flappy ass. Give me that big, flappy ass.
"肉颤 肉颤 肉颤颤的丰臀 我想你的奶子想得要命"
Give me, give me, flappy dappy, floppity, sucking titties."
快照哦
Snapchat.
欢迎加入奥巴比健保社
Welcome to o'Bobbycare.
请在这里签字 给俺你的会员费
Now just sign here, and give me your premium.
- 好的 Bobby - 这比俺想得简单得多
- Okay, Bobby. - This is easier than I thought.
只要你不受伤 一切就都好说
As long as you don't get hurt, everything will be okay.
- 我眼睛里有支铅笔 Bobby - 老天 Bodean 你得过点细啊
- I got a pencil stuck in my eye, Bobby. - Jesus, Bodean, you gotta be careful.
现在我眼睛里有两只铅笔 Bobby
Now I got two pencils stuck in my eye, Bobby.
别望你眼里插铅笔了
Stop sticking pencils in your eye.
- 搞毛啊 Bodean - 怎么? 钢笔也不行?
- Damn it, Bodean. - What? Pens too?
Steve 向左转
Steve, turn left.
- 我左边还是你左边? - 都特么是一个左边好吧
- - My left or your left? - They're the same goddamn left.
靠 Steve 快滚起来
Shit! Steve, get your ass up!
如诸位所见 我长出个傻X
As you can all see, I have grown a dork.
Woody 告我疼不疼
Woody, tell me if this hurts.
你俩现在能出院了么?
Shouldn't you two still be in the hospital?
咋地? 让我断了三十年如一日出勤记录?
What? And ruin my perfect attendance record?
绝逼不行 该咋上班咋上班
Hell, no. It's business as usual.
现在说下...
Now let's get ser...
- 挠痒痒噜 - 停
- Tickle fight. - Stop!
我向天发誓 Steve
I swear to God, Steve.
你为神马这么刻薄嘛 火爆肥仔先森?
Why are you so mean, Mr. Grumpy Lumps?
好了 开始张罗疯狂派对 Denzel 上安保报告
Now let's have a [Bleep] party. Denzel, security report.
你那屋所有电器都让我拿到当铺了
I took all your electronics down to the pawn shop.
因为吧 人家得把里面的脏弹给拆了
Uh, yeah, they defuse dirty bombs down there.
干得漂亮 好了 该吃午饭了 大家伙
Good job. Okay. That's lunch, everybody.
1983年发源于美国的连锁餐厅
走着 肝仔 我们去吃猫头鹰餐厅
Come on, liver boy, we're going to Hooters.
抱歉 午饭时我要排练 不能不去诶
Sorry, I practice over lunch, and I can't miss it.
练毛?
Practice what?
♪ 我如此喜爱清唱 ♪
I like to sing a capella...
- 我恨清唱 清唱是傻X - ♪ 变成最快乐的孩子 ♪
- Oh, I hate a capella. A capella sucks! - ♪ Makes me a most happy fella ♪
- 住嘴 住嘴 - ♪ 听我馥郁芬芳的喉咙 ♪
- Stop it. Stop it. - ♪ I sing songs loud or mellow ♪
♪ 妹子们全都自动躺倒 ♪
♪ all the girls' legs turn to jell-o ♪
你帮我洗洗我帮你洗洗会不会更健康?
How about I wash yours, and you wash mine?
不要
Nooo!
脆莓医疗中心 Kuzniak医生坐诊
你有入保险没?
Do you have insurance?
有啊 钱都交给他了
Yep, he's right there.
行吧 走你
Okay, here we go.
- 总共1200刀 - 1200刀?
- That'll be $1,200. - $1,200?
不用谢我 要谢就谢这世上最棒的健保制度吧
Don't thank me. Thank the greatest health care system in the world.
我决定了 Bodean 你被"奥巴比健保"除名了
That's it, Bodean. I am dropping you from o'Bobbycare.
但根据"奥巴比健保手册"第一条规定 你无权除名呢 Bobby
Well, according to page one of the o'Bobbycare manual, you can't do that, Bobby.
奥巴比健保手"厕"
我靠 求你告诉我 你身上没别的毛病了
Damn it. Please tell me there's nothing else wrong with you.
甭担心 Bobby 俺就是有点高血压 高血糖 憩室炎 大肠炎
Don't worry, Bobby... I just got high blood pressure, high sugar, diverticulitis, colitis,
牙龈炎 丁日热 还有JJ生疮而已
gingivitis, bieber fever, and sores on my Peter.
不要啊 别这样 妈咪
No, no, mommy.
♪ 乖乖睡吧 宝贝 不要吵 ♪
♪ Hush, little baby, don't say a word ♪
♪ 妈妈给你油炸大粪糕 ♪
♪ mama's gonna fry you a talking turd ♪
不知道你昨晚做了啥
Wow, I don't know what you did,
自我妈把我饿到昏迷以来
but that is the best night of sleep I've had
这算是我睡得最香的一晚了
since my mom starved me into a coma.
- 感觉好极了 - 等你尝过这个再说
- I feel incredible. - Wait till you try this.
感觉就像椰子天使在我嘴里拉屎一样
It's like a coconut angel took a shit in my mouth.
- 谢谢表扬 - 知道吗 Steve 我以为绝不可能说这种话 但...
- Thanks. - You know what, Steve? I never thought I'd say it, but...
我开始不那么恨你了
but I'm starting to hate you a little less.
♪ 做我 做我 做我 做我 做我的好基友 ♪
♪ Be my, be my, be my, be my, be my, be my BFF ♪
♪ 好基友一被子 甭管经历什么事 ♪
♪ best friends forever, whatever we endeavor ♪
♪ 肝连肝 不分离 ♪
♪ our bond won't ever sever ♪
♪ 不管啥事都在一起 ♪
♪ no matter whatso-whatsoever ♪
♪ 好基友 不分离 ♪
♪ Best friends forever, whatever... ♪
♪ 永远在一起 ♪
♪ together wherever ♪
♪ 好开心身旁就有你 ♪
♪ I'm happy settled in between ♪
♪ 做我 做我 做我 做我 做我的好基友 ♪
♪ be my, be my, be my, be my, be my, be my BFF ♪
♪ 哦 好基友 ♪
♪ oh, best friend ♪
我就说这个洞会有福利的
医院
好啦 咱们的48小时差不多过完了
Well, I guess our 48 hours is almost up.
如果我要跟谁做连体手术的话
If I had to be surgically attached to anybody,
- 我很高兴那个人是你 Steve - 真的? 谢啦 老兄
- I'm glad it was you, Steve. - Really? Thanks, buddy.
好啦 时间到 Woody
Well, it's time, Woody.
你真走运 今天没有同性恋非法移民需要植肝
Lucky for you, there's not one single gay, illegal immigrant who needs a liver today.
偶爆肝了
My liver exploded.
糟了
Oh, not good.
你们知道"倒血霉"这个医学名词不?
Are you familiar with a medical term called "jinxing"?
看起来你得跟Steve一起参加你的受勋仪式了
Yeah. Looks like you'll be stuck with Steve for your event.
我靠啊 不会吧 我怎么老遇到这种破事?
God damn it, no! How could this happen to me?
Woody 有啥大不了的? 咱们一起去就得了
Woody, what's the big deal? We'll just go together.
有啥了不起的?
"What's the big deal?"
老子告诉过你一千遍了 Steve 老子不要你在场
I've told you a thousand times, Steve! I don't want you there!
我 我还以为现在咱俩关系不同了
But I-I thought things were different now.
- 我还以为你喜欢我了 - 啥都没变
- I thought you liked me. - Nothing is different.
摊上那种破事 我只是想好过点而已
I was just making the best of a shitty situation.
老子不喜欢你 永远也不会
I don't like you, and I never will!
你不配有我这样的朋友
You don't deserve a friend like me.
你俩能别处去闹吗?
Can you fellows take this argument someplace else?
我这里有非法移民要做手术呢
I have an illegal to operate on.
此处anesthesia既指麻醉 也指人名
我要麻醉
I need anesthesia.
蔴蕞?
Anesthesia?
吵啥吵 草泥马 老娘刚要睡着
What you want, mother[Bleep]? I'm tryin' to sleep!
- 你特么吃啥呢你? - 生培根
- What the hell are you eating? - Raw bacon.
- 不许你生吃培根 - 行吧
- You can't eat raw bacon. - All right, then,
那我喝这杯94盎司的可乐好了
I'll just drink this 94-ounce Coca-Cola.
生培根弄得我好渴
Raw bacon makes me thirsty.
其实 我禁止你喝大杯饮料 吃生培根
Well, I'm banning big sodas, raw bacon,
以及其它任何可能弄废你的东西 包括枪支
and anything else that'll [Bleep] you up, including guns.
枪也不行? 那我撸管时嘴里该放点啥?
Guns? What am I gonna put in my mouth when I jack off?
- 你为啥这样对我 Bobby? - 因为如果你病了或者受伤
- Why are you doing this, Bobby? - Because if you get sick or hurt,
埋单的可是老子 你个蠢杂种
I'm gonna have to pay for it, you dumb son of a bitch.
知道不? "奥巴比"把我爱的一切都夺走了
You know what? O'Bobbycare took away everything I love.
奥巴马才不会像这样伤害我
Obama would never hurt me like this.
对啊 他真是个混蛋 真受不了他
Yeah, he's a real jerk. I can't stand him.
没有 他就在我旁边
No. He's right next to me
美国女演员 导演
还留着他那撮凯瑟琳·特纳式的傻X大胡子
with his big, stupid Kathleen Turner mustache.
干你娘 那个电话是假的好吧
[Bleep] You. That's not even a real phone.
- 知道他什么人了吧? - 唐氏综合症患者?
- See what I'm dealing with? - Down syndrome?
俗称先天愚型 患病儿童常智力低下
我为你准备了个惊喜哟 Steve
I've got a surprise for you, Steve.
盒子里是什么?
What's in the box?
美国女演员
大家都希望是格温妮丝·帕特洛的脑袋吧
I think we're all hoping it's Gwyneth Paltrow's head.
马上你们就知道了
Oh, you'll see.
这法宝能防止你搞砸了我的大事
It's my plan to keep you from screwing up my event
同时还能让我像个英雄
and make me look like a hero in the process.
Woody? Woody 别啊
Woody? Woody, no!
别这样 别这样 你这是干嘛?
No, no, no, no! What are you doing?
欢迎奥巴马
- 今晚的主角原来在这儿哪 - 嘿 见到你很高兴
- Ah, here is the man of the hour. - Hey, great to see you.
你身边的这位是?
And who is your guest?
这小子得了癌症 我救了他一命
This is a cancer kid. I saved his life,
把他缝到我身上 他就可以用上我的肝
had him sewn to me, so he could share my liver.
癌症把他的肝废了
The cancer took his.
老天爷 你叫什么名字 孩子?
Dear God. What's your name, son?
忘了告诉你 他还是个哑巴 而且脑子基本瘫了
Did I mention he's also a mute and pretty much brain dead?
那他就是个脑瘫的哑巴咯?
So he's brain dead and a mute?
本来他可以说话的 可惜扁桃体得了癌
Well, he wasn't born a mute. He had tonsil cancer.
我还以为他得的是肝癌
Oh, I thought he had liver cancer.
的确有肝癌 他这是两头堵
Oh, he does. He's getting it from both ends.
癌症在这脑残小杂种身上开火车一样蹿来蹿去
Cancer's running a train on this brain-dead bastard.
不打扰你们了 玩得开心点
Well, have a splendid time.
你这招实在太贱 我永远都不会原谅你的
This sucks. I'll never forgive you for this.
你闭好嘴巴就行
You just keep your mouth shut.
别给我瞎胡闹 你个废物
You're not screwing this up for me, you annoying waste of space.
- 你好 Varnadoe议员 - 您身边这位是谁?
- Oh, hello, Senator Varnadoe. - And who is this with you?
就是个得了癌的脑残哑巴而已
Just a shit-for-brains cancer mute.
他没几天活头了 无视他就行
He'll be dead soon, so just pretend he's not here.
- 来点蟹饼吗 先生们? - 我不用 我过敏过得厉害
- Crab cakes, gentlemen? - Not for me. I'm highly allergic.
的确 这真是无上的光荣 哇 怎么突然好热
Yes, this is truly an honor. Whoa, did it get hot in here?
- Johnson先生 您还好吗? - 好好 好得不得了
- Mr. Johnson, are you feeling okay? - Yeah, yeah, I never felt better.
大家注意 总统已到
Attention, everyone, the president has arrived.
记住了 Connie 别跟现实脱节
Now remember, Connie, keep in touch with reality.
你瞧着吧
You'll see.
- 你好 "小巴" - Connie
- Hello, Barry. - Connie!
- 不好意思 我认识你吗? - 别装了
- I'm sorry, do I know you? - You should.
上周你都发了一百多条下流短信给人家了 你个色狼
You've sent me over a hundred dirty texts in the last week, you pervert.
这家伙谁? 有点搞笑哈
Who is this guy? He's funny.
别再缠着我 我是认真的
Leave me alone. I mean it.
别过来 滚开
No, no.
你好呀 Connie
Hello, Connie.
你知不知道 刚才假装不认识你有多难?
Do you know how hard it was to pretend I didn't know you back there?
我编出这个傻X奖项 为的只是接近你
I had to make up this stupid award just to get close to you.
不行 Barry 我告诉过你好多次了 我是女同
No, Barry. I've told you a hundred times, I'm a lesbian.
我老婆也是啊
So was Michelle.
哥就喜欢挑战
I like a challenge.
你闻起来就像星期天的动物园一样
You smell like a petting zoo on a hot Sunday.
- 别这样 - 还记得我们第一次见面那天
- Stop it. - I remember the first day we met.
你白花花的大屁股 看得我也是醉了
I was intoxicated by that big, pasty ass.
从那以后 我就一直追寻着你这头红发小母龙
I've been chasing that ginger dragon ever since.
Barry 你都结婚了 我们不可以这样
Barry, you're a married man. We can't.
语出奥巴马2010年大选获胜演说
我们可以的 Connie 我们当然可以
Yes, we can, Connie. Yes, we can.
总统先生 该您上台了
Mr. president, it's time to go on.
靠 我马上过去
Damn. I'll be right there.
待会再来玩你肉颤颤的丰腴大屁股
I'll be back for that big flappy, dappy ass.
请欢迎美利坚合众国总统
Please welcome the President of the United States,
巴拉克·奥巴马
Barack Obama.
很荣幸在这样意义非凡的日子来到这里
It's a privilege to be here on this special day
给这位杰出的美国公民授勋
to honor a great American
同时也向我国雄伟壮观的国家公园之一脆莓公园致敬
and one of our nation's majestic national parks, Brickleberry.
国家公园风景辽阔 美不胜收
National parks are both big and beautiful
肉颤颤而丰腴
and flappy dappy.
这小子说得真好
The man is a good speaker.
接下来 言归正传
So, without further adieu,
我向大家介绍今天的焦点
I'd like to introduce the man of the hour,
他对自己救下的罹患癌症的脑瘫哑巴仍然不离不弃
accompanied by the brain-dead, mute cancer kid whose life he saved.
女士们先生们 请欢迎Woody Johnson先生
Ladies and gentlemen, Mr. Woody Johnson.
美国女演员
看啊 莉娜·杜汉姆出场了
Hey, look, it's Lena Dunham.
长这样还露脸 心太宽了
She's so brave.
这位好人不仅多次救助过罹患癌症的儿童
Now, this man not only saves cancer-stricken children's lives,
而且更重要的是 几十年如一日地按时上班
but more importantly, shows up for work every day,
因此 我要把这个奖颁发给您
and so I present this award to you.
谢谢您 总统先...
Thank you, Mr. presid...
壮哉美国 美国最高 美国加油
U.S.A.! U.S.A.! U.S.A.!
天哪 怎么会变成这样?
Oh, God, how did this happen?
该不会是我吃的那盘蟹饼的问题吧?
Hmm, it wasn't that tray of crab cakes I ate, was it?
你害的我? 你个王八犊子
You did this? You son of a bitch,
你毁了我人生中最好的一天
you ruined the best day of my life!
要不是我 你有个屁的人生
You wouldn't have a life if it wasn't for me.
我只是想跟你做朋友
I just wanted to be your friend,
你却像对待一坨翔一样对待我
and all you did was treat me like shit.
还说我有癌症什么的
And you gave me cancer.
- 老子要宰了你 - 我先宰了你再说
- I'm gonna kill you. - Not if I kill you first.
Johnson先生 我是福克斯新闻频道的
Mr. Johnson, I'm from Fox News.
因为您吐了总统一身
I'd like to present you
我特此向您颁发我们的"年度人物"奖
with our "man of the year" award for puking all over the president.
干得漂亮 先生
Well done, sir.
哎哟 我都不知道说什么好
Oh, my God, I don't know what to say.
真是太荣幸了
What an honor.
这可比总统的什么傻X奖章强多了
Well, this beats the shit out of a stupid presidential medal,
这一切都应该归功于我的朋友Steve
and I owe it all to my friend Steve.
- 我们是朋友? 真的? - 绝对的 老弟
- We're friends? Really? - You bet, buddy.
抱歉我之前太混蛋了
Sorry for being such a dick.
我想其实我俩都学到了宝贵的一课
I guess we all learned a good lesson today.
来点美味的蟹饼好好巩固下这一课怎么样?
Why don't you wash that lesson down with some delicious crab cakes?
好主意哦 Malloy
Oh, great idea, Malloy.
别吃 Steve 别 我过敏...
No, Steve, no! I'm highly allerg...
- 嘿 Bobby - 说过了 Bodean 我一分钱都没了
- Hey, Bobby. - I told you, Bodean, I'm flat broke.
- 不能再带你去看医生了 - 没关系的 Bobby
- I can't take you to the doctor. - That's okay, Bobby.
等血流干 我挂了也就不疼了
The pain will go away when I bleed out and die.
我真希望你像我一样有个可靠的健保制度
I sure do wish you had dependable health coverage like I do.
我都不知道你有健保
I didn't know you had health insurance.
有啊 我花光所有钱付清你的医药费破产之后
Yeah, after I spent all that money on your medical bills and went broke,
就符合入奥巴马健保的条件了 叼爆了
I qualified for Obamacare. It's awesome.
只可惜我没法儿捞点好处
Too bad there ain't no way to get on your policy.
办法倒是有一个
Well, there is one way.
我现在宣布你俩结为"夫夫"
I now pronounce you husband and husband.
下地狱玩个快活吧
Have fun in hell.
好消息啊 Bodean
Well, good news, Bodean,
因为我们现在算正式结了婚 你现在有健保啦
you got insurance now, because we're officially married.
不交媾算啥正式结婚
It ain't official until we consummate it.
Connie 真走运他们没有告你
Connie, you're lucky they didn't commit you.
我说的一直都是大实话
I was telling the truth the whole time.
总统真的好想占有我
Barack really does want me.
喂
Hello?
Connie 昨晚不辞而别真是抱歉
Connie, I'm sorry I got swept away last night.
我很快就会回去玩你的肉屁股
I'll be back for that flappy ass soon.
而且 我送了你个小礼物先让你解解馋
In the meantime, I sent a present to tide you over.
让我猜猜 又是"小巴"对吧?
Let me guess. That was "Barry," right?
是啊 他说送了我个小礼物
Yep, and he said he sent me a present.
到底会是什么呢...
I wonder what it could...
恶心 奥巴马发了张JJ照给我
Gross. Obama sent me a dick pic.
- 这只是黑屏好吧 - 这是特写
- It's just a black screen. - It's a close up!
欢迎微博关注@漫迪字幕组
weibo.com/weheartcartoons